<?xml version="1.0"?>
<feed>
  <tips>
    <title>Offer and Package</title>
    <message>
      Clients are more prone to purchase several services if they are offered.
      Make sure that you offer as many pertinent products and services as possible.
    </message>
  </tips>
  <tips>
    <title>Clarify, Then Verify</title>
    <message>
      Make sure to clarify the information that the client just gave such as
      phone number, social security number, name, etc.
    </message>
  </tips>
  <tips>
    <title>Offer What's Needed</title>
    <message>
      Do not sell the client an internet speed higher than what they need.
    </message>
  </tips>
  <tips>
    <title>Autopay Saves The Day</title>
    <message>
      Offer the client the option to use our Automatic Withdrawal option for ease and
      convenience for paying their bills.
    </message>
  </tips>
  <tips>
    <title>Shred it! Don't Forget it!</title>
    <message>
      Please make sure to properly shred any confidential information that is written down.
    </message>
  </tips>
  <tips>
    <title>It's Not You. It's Me.</title>
    <message>
      If a client becomes irate, do not take it personally. Remember, they are mad at the
      situation, not you.
    </message>
  </tips>
  <tips>
    <title>Build Trust First!</title>
    <message>
      Clients give objections when they don't feel the need to buy, are unclear about something,
      or trust hasn't been established. Don't be afraid to ask the client why they are
      objecting to your proposed service.
    </message>
  </tips>
  <tips>
    <title>You Were Listening? What'd I Say?</title>
    <message>
      Listen attentively. Clients get the feeling that you are not paying attention if they
      keep having to repeat themselves.
    </message>
  </tips>
  <tips>
    <title>Can't Buy Me Love!</title>
    <message>
      Focus on value rather than price. A client can always find a lower price, so we need
      to sell the value.
    </message>
  </tips>
  <tips>
    <title>What's The Password?</title>
    <message>
      Always verify last 4 of the social security number when client's call in. We are
      not to give out information to unauthorized parties.
    </message>
  </tips>
  <tips>
	<title>Time is money</title>
	<message>
		While we do offer 7 day a week installation, please do your utmost to steer the client
		to installation dates during business hours. However, if a weekend install is the only
		arrangement that will satisfy them, gladly comply.
	</message>
  </tips>
</feed>